Class of 1918 Records, 1914-1988
Smith College Archives
Class of 1918 Records
1914-1988
Smith College. Class of 1918.
RG 80 UUID:0373a3b1-24aa-4e69-af40-1b4cdebd2ced
22 boxes (19.4 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1918.
The Class of 1918 was the fortieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1918 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1918, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, treasury information, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1918 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Carmen Saeculare of Horace 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 4)
- Dues Ledger 1953-1983 (Box 1907, Folder 5)
- Freshman Frolic 1914 (Box 1907, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind 1914 (Box 1907, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1914-1915 (Box 1907, Folder 8)
- Freshman Party 1914 (Box 1907, Folder 9)
- Groups 1914-1918 (Box 1907, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 11)
- Junior Frolic 1917 (Box 1907, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom 1917 (Box 1907, Folder 13)
- Class Letters 1926-1978 (Box 1907, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1926-1977 (Box 1907, Folder 15)
- Memorials 1978 (Box 1907, Folder 16)
- Organization 1916-1917 (Box 1907, Folder 17)
- Photographs undated (Box 1907, Folder 18)
- Class President's Notebook 1914-1918 (Box 1907, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1918-1922 (Box 1908, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Photographs 1922 (Box 1908, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1923 (Box 1908, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1928 (Box 1908, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 1908, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 1908, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1908, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 1908, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 1908, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 1908, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1908, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1973-1975 (Box 1908, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 1908, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 1908, Folder 14)
- Seal, Emblem, Animal, etc. undated (Box 1908.1, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Correspondence 1984-1988 (Box 1908.1, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics 1918 (Box 1908.1, Folder 3)
- Songs undated (Box 1908.1, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Carnival 1916 (Box 1908.1, Folder 5)
- Sophomore Reception 1916 (Box 1908.1, Folder 6)
- Class Supper 1918 (Box 1908.1, Folder 7)
- Class Tax 1906-1966 (Box 1908.1, Folder 8)
- Class Treasurer 1964-1981 (Box 1908.1, Folder 9)
- Treasurer's Correspondence 1945-1966 (Box 1908.1, Folder 10)
- Treasurer's Account Ledger 1915-1972 (Box 1908.1, Folder 11)
- Treasurer's Account Ledger 1973-1983 (Box 1908.1, Folder 12)
- Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box OV)